<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prerequisites on AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) Workshop</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites.html</link><description>Recent content in Prerequisites on AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) Workshop</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS CLI</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/100-awscli.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/100-awscli.html</guid><description>The AWS CLI allows you to interact with AWS services from a terminal session. Make sure you have the latest version of the AWS CLI installed on your system.
Windows: MSI installer Linux, macOS or Unix: Bundled installer See the AWS Command Line Interface installation page for more details.</description></item><item><title>AWS Account and User</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/200-account.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/200-account.html</guid><description>AWS Account for Experimentation To deploy our app, you&amp;rsquo;ll need access to an AWS account. If you already have an account and your system is configured with credentials of an administrator user, you can move to the next step.
If you are using an existing account, either personal or a company account, make sure you understand the implications and policy of provisioning resources into this account.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have an AWS account, you can create a free account here.</description></item><item><title>Node.js</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/300-nodejs.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/300-nodejs.html</guid><description>The AWS CDK uses Node.js (&amp;gt;= 10.13.0, except for versions 13.0.0 - 13.6.0). A version in active long-term support (16.x at this writing) is recommended.
To install Node.js visit the node.js website.
Windows: if you have an old version of Node.js installed on your system, it may be required to run the .msi installation as Administrator. If you already have Node.js installed, verify that you have a compatible version:
node --version Output should be &amp;gt;= 10.</description></item><item><title>IDE for your programming language</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/400-ide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/400-ide.html</guid><description>One of the benefits of the AWS CDK is that you can leverage your favorite development environments and have a rich experience when exploring the hundreds of different services and features of AWS.
We highly recommend to use an IDE that supports code-completion and syntax highlighting for your language of choice:
VSCode (recommended) AWS Cloud9 Atom with the atom-typescript plugin vim with tsuquyomi WebStorm Emacs with the tide mode PyCharm Eclipse</description></item><item><title>AWS CDK Toolkit</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/500-toolkit.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/500-toolkit.html</guid><description>Next, we&amp;rsquo;ll install the AWS CDK Toolkit. The toolkit is a command-line utility which allows you to work with CDK apps.
Open a terminal session and run the following command:
Windows: you&amp;rsquo;ll need to run this as an Administrator POSIX: on some systems you may need to run this with sudo npm install -g aws-cdk You can check the toolkit version:
$ cdk --version 2.0.0 (build 4b6ce31)</description></item><item><title>Python</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/600-python.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/600-python.html</guid><description>If you are planning on using the Python Workshop, you obviously will need to have Python installed. Specifically, you will need version 3.6 or later. You can find information about downloading and installing Python here.
If you use Windows, be sure Python is on your PATH. To see if it is, type python at a command prompt. The easiest way to make sure Python is on your PATH is to tick the Add Python 3.</description></item><item><title>.NET</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/700-dotnet.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/700-dotnet.html</guid><description>If you are planning on using the .NET Workshop, you obviously will need to have the .NET Core SDK installed. Specifically, you will need version 3.1 or later. You can find information about downloading and installing .NET Core SDK here.
We will be using the .NET Core CLI for this project, so if you are not familiar, please take a look at their documentation.</description></item><item><title>Java</title><link>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/800-java.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdkworkshop.com/15-prerequisites/800-java.html</guid><description>If you are planning on using the Java Workshop, you obviously will need to have a JDK installed. Specifically, you will need JDK 11 or later. You can find information about downloading and installing the Amazon Corretto 11 distribution here. Other JDK 11 distributions are available if you do not wish to use Amazon Corretto.</description></item></channel></rss>